Namrata kanda

Surrey, BC, Canada | (778) 551-9708 | namrata.aeri@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/namrata-kanda/

Profile

With a diverse background in both retail and software engineering, complemented by volunteering as a graphic designer, I bring a unique blend of customer service ability and technical proficiency. My experience spans from addressing customer inquiries and processing transactions to enhancing user experiences and fixing critical software issues.

Education

Web and Android Development Jan 2024 - Present

Langara College, Vancouver, Canada

Experience

CGI | Associate Software Engineer

Sept 2022 - Oct 2023

- Worked with the QA Team to handle customer issues & Gave training to new joiners
- Fixed Critical and high customer issues to keep the quality of the application
- Enhanced the user experience by implementing new functionalities
- Attended CSR activities to help society and connect with people
- Attended the agile daily stand ups with other members and delivered daily updates to management
- Coordinated the team responsibilities for monitoring the performance of the team
- Improved the performance of the application by perfecting the code

LingaROS | Junior Software Engineer

Sept 2021 - Sept 2022

- Worked with the BA Team to develop new features
- Worked with the QA Team to improve the quality of the application
- Bug fixing to improve performance
- Learning innovative technologies to update the application and developed responsive web Pages

Skills & Abilities

Technical Skills: Visual Studio, Windows, Linux, Retail Software, JIRA, Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, MongoDB, Firebase, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Python, Git, WordPress, Graphic Designing, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Payment Devices

Soft Skills: Problem solving, Organizational skills, Risk Management, Multitasking, Teamwork, Customer Service, Time management, Attention to Detail, Adaptability

Volunteering Experience: Brand Identity Designer for Langara Punjabi Association (Langara College), Volunteered for Pet therapy, Seminars, etc at on-campus and off-campus events.